thepcmanwebsite.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy - The PCman Website

## The PCman's Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**General Policy**  
This Privacy Policy was created in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our visitors privacy. The following discloses our information gathering, no email spam and dissemination practices for this website.

For each visitor to our web pages, our web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's domain name, but not their e-mail address. We collect the domain name and browser information of visitors to our website. We track visitors' paths through our site to help improve the quality and content of our website. The information collected is used to improve the content of our site and serve advertisements. It is collected for us by third-party organizations for the purpose of analysis and ad serving. It is common practice for webmasters to track visitors on their site. You may opt-out of [Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout), our traffic analysis program.

The PCman Website uses SSL encryption on all our pages to further protect the privacy of our visitors. Click the SSL seal above to verify the validity of the encryption.

**Advertisements**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website to pay for our operating costs. This is how we offer all our services for free. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [here](https://www.aboutads.info/). This link will show you [how Google uses this data](https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners). View our [cookie policy](https://www.thepcmanwebsite.com/cookie-policy.shtml) to learn more about opting out of third-party advertising. 

**Cookies**  
Visit our network [cookie policy](https://www.thepcmanwebsite.com/cookie-policy.shtml) page to learn about what cookies are, the cookies that are used on this site, how they add functionality to this site and how they can be enabled, disabled, deleted and managed. When a visitor continues to browse this site they are agreeing to our use of cookies and the manner in which they are being used. If a visitor disagrees with this policy they must leave this site immediately.

**Posting to a Webpage/Database**  
Our visitors should be aware that when you disclose your personal information in our guestbook or other publicly viewable page your information will be added to an online web page, this does make your information viewable by all visitors. This does not include our web tools or our contact forms, only pages where your information is posted to a web page. At the appropriate time you will be notified that this is going to take place and will be given the option to discontinue that action.

**Business Card Directory**  
Any information that you submit to your business card is only posted to our directory if you have chosen that option, it is NOT mandatory to post online. The business card directory will post all information you enter onto your card. Remove any information on your card you don't want to be public before you post it online. 

**Resume Directory**  
Any information that you enter on your resume is only posted to our directory if you have chosen that option, it is NOT mandatory to post online. The resume directory does not display your street address, telephone number or cellphone number. The directory will display your name, city, state, objectives, all of your employment and education history and anything you entered into the Additional spaces. Your email address is displayed in an obscured but human readable form so employers may contact you. You have the option at any point to login and remove your resume from the directory, edit your resume or delete the whole account.

**Job Search Directory**  
When employers post ads to our directory they must assume all the information they enter, excluding their login information, will be publicly visible. This should seem reasonable since the whole point of the listing is to make this information public to attract candidates for employment. This information is only used to provide the listing. Any information an employer wishes to remain private should not be entered into the system. Job postings may be edited and removed or the account may deleted at the discretion of the employer.

**Newsletter/Surveys/Comments/Testimonials**  
For visitors that sign up for our Newsletter your name and email address is only used for the purpose of delivering the newsletter and never, ever given to external organizations. We vehemently oppose the undesirable practice of email SPAM so your information is held in strict confidence. You have the ability to opt-out if you wish. Any information submitted in a survey or comments is only used internally to improve the quality of our service. We may use your testimonial comments publicly on one of our pages.

**Web Tools/Slogan Creator**  
We do not keep track of the information visitors enter to create slogans, webmaster tools, etc. Unless the visitor is specifically given the choice to post their information online none of it is stored by us.

**Contacting Us**  
If you contact us using a form or by an email client on your device we do not use that information for anything other than responding your inquiry. If you have any questions or concerns about how one of our programs that you wish to use and how will use your personal information please contact us for more specific information.

**Child Access**  
Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from providing their personal information on this site without parental permission.

Thank you,

The PCman Website Staff 

#### New features are always added so check back often.
